citiesads.in 2010-11-20

# Free classified Ads India | Online Classifieds India | Online Classified Advertising | Post Free Local Classified ad Listings in India - Citiesads.ini

**CitiesAds Privacy statement**

We understand and appreciate the fact that our customers are concerned about the privacy afforded to their information collected when dealing with us. We are committed to providing our customers with a high level of privacy in relation to the personal information that is collected whilst dealing with CitiesAds. To display this commitment, we provide the following privacy statement for our customer’s viewing.  

**Personal Information Collected**

The type of information generally collected by CitiesAds includes your name, address, telephone number, facsimile number, e-mail address and photographic identification number. This information is collected in order for CitiesAds.to perform the services that you have requested.  

**Information We Collect**

In order to ensure that consumers get the very best service, CitiesAds. ie collects demographic information, web pages visited and other consumer-volunteered information from sources such as forms, survey information and/or site registrations. CitiesAds. ie’s request forms may require users to give us information such as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address information. This information gathering procedure allows CitiesAds. ie to match you with a dealer or partner that we feel is best able to fulfill your request. This information also helps Auto-Deal.ie in the development or referral of products and services that we believe will meet the continuing needs of our customers. Collected information is used to improve the content of our website, customize the content and/or layout of our website for individual users, and to contact users for marketing purposes as well as route requests to our auto dealer network, fulfillment and marketing partners. Should you request an autoloan quote, such information will be distributed to our partners for credit checks and loan approval.   

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page frequently for changes. Your continued use of the CitiesAds. ie site means you accept those changes. You can e-mail us with any further questions you may have.
